hi team um hope all doing good now I
come up with General Insurance
Corporation of
India uh this is into reinsurance
business so the disclaimer as usual uh
this is my personal view only
uh this is only educational purpose I'm
not a SE registered adviser do your own
research and take your financial advisor
cons uh uh consult your financial
advisor for the next step I'm not
responsible for any profit and loss on
this stock in fact I'm not investing at
this stage as I
said um now let us move as I said it's a
personal view
only so I always
uh likes to look at from the higher time
frame like monthly weekly daily now if
you look at this
stock it has fallen ever since uh listed
and thereafter say it listed around
430 uh 425 levels and then it bottomed
at around um 81 level right and now
again it is coming back to the same high
as a resistance level so if You observe
that this stock has fallen straight away
from the 425 opening
levels to
156 so this is one way fall then
retraced and then again it fall so if
You observe what has happened that point
of time with the volume
side when it went upside
here volume are very Less in fact I
don't say that's not a volume so
maybe uh you know some people might
wants to exit so then they pulled up
high then it's a kind of you know uh
manifested move kind of what I believe
that because it has not got sustained
that's a
reason after that if you look at the
situation uh it has been Consolidated uh
it's not like exactly Consolidated all
in fact it tried to go up again and then
it came back so it spend almost you know
the major time here between 2022 2023 uh
I mean till this uh the UPC the this
recent breakout
here so during this point of time also
you know uh volumes are not such big but
yeah whenever low is coming up it has
been accumulated so if you obs Ober that
it has taken a base
here around these levels it formed the
base
now right so around one 100 something
like
that but stock has in recent weeks if I
switch it two weeks if you look at that
just in three weeks it went High just in
three weeks you know in 3 weeks it went
almost 50% from
223 as a low
and uh 335 is a high so almost 50%
uh uh High it went uh within 3 weeks
itself
okay okay so almost 50% up here so if
you look at that again here when it is
went like the same way there were no
volumes but this time when it is going
up there are volumes
and in fact at this
location it has been accumulated more
before going to the next uh breakout so
what I'm trying to say that here if you
look at it's going to be a multi-year
breakout kind of like in 19 the high was
334 and now in 2023 the height is
so the idea
is uh in a lowrisk
situation this is where the rally has
been started in fact uh from this candle
uh the rally has been started but I'm
considering this as a you know these
days Vol is very high that's a reason so
if I take
this how much the low is
22 it will be two far
I mean very
conservative candidates can take it here
but otherwise I can see that here it has
been bottomed in 3 weeks continuously so
which was around 222 something like that
this could be
yourl
okay and then when it comes to
Target
it
will go back to the same reent I mean
same the uh last 52 weeks High
4495 you got
it but give some space I mean uh don't
be hurry
uh uh let the pullback can come so in
that case what I can see that say if I
look at this 15 minutes uh
location uh see this is where uh from
264 to 335 it went like rapidly so maybe
what I can think that it might come
around uh 290 levels something like that
see sometimes what will happen before
before coming to
the before coming to the expected uh
area it might turn up
again so around this 295 290 will be
good price maybe because see we need to
bargain before buying only so we should
not enter in hurry so be careful about
that so that's what I can see uh in this
stock thank you